

ĐỖ PHÚ KHƯƠNG

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

9

Go Vap District, Ho Chi Minh City

SUMMARY

I am a Web Developer. I have 2 years of work experience in building web applications (JavaScript, C#). I am a ordinary person with a simple in appearance and mind. I like reaching and challenging many new things. Furthermore, Developer is a suitable field for people who love exploring new ones. So that's why I want to become a coder. I am looking to participate in new projects so that i can gain more knowledge and experience for myself in technology and multidisciplinary knowledge. Here are a few of my thoughts about myself, thanks for reading and It would be great to have a meeting of us. Thank you so much.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages:

C# JavaScript Java

• Frameworks/Platforms:

ASP.NET MVC, Dotnet Framework, Dotnet Core 6.0, Entity Framework JavaScript, Jquery, Ajax, Bootstrap, ReactJS Spring MVC Boot

Database

NoSQL: MongoDB

SQL: MS SQL, MySQL, PostgreSQL

Version Control:

Sub version, Git

• Foreign Languages:

English

Soft Skills:

Teamwork or work independently

• Others:

Always has an urge in researching and learning efficient ways to approach the problems.

WORK EXPERIENCE

KAS TECHNOLOGY CORPORATION

09/2020 - 03/2021: SMAC CLOUD System UI Upgrade.

Front end Developer

- Description: Upgrade the company's Enterprise Resource Planning product interface.
- Technologies Used: Html, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, RestfulAPI.
- Teamsize: 3 Frontend, 1 Backend.

03/2021 - 06/2022: R&D and upgrade SMAC CLOUD System.

Frontend & Backend Developer

- Description: Exchange and analyze operations and utilities related to CRM, HRM, Sale, Revenue, expenditure, analysis reports, dashboards...
- Technologies Used: Html, CSS, JavaScript, Jquery, Bootstrap, RestfulAPI, Dotnet Framework, database MongoDB.
- Teamsize: 5 Frontend, 3 Backend, 1 BA.

04/2022 - 06/2022: Customize Enterprise Resource Planning system for DussMann.

Frontend & Backend Developer

- Description: Building a system to order meals for employees according to customers' specific operations.
- Technologies Used: Html, CSS, JavaScript, Jquery, Bootstrap, RestfulAPI, Dotnet Framework, database MongoDB.
- Teamsize: 1 Frontend, 2 Backend, 1 BA.

06/2022 - 11/2022: General accounting system.

Backend Developer

- Description: Building an accounting system for storing, accounting according to accounting accounts and querying reports.
- Technologies Used: Dotnet core 6.0, Entity Framework, RestfulAPI, database Postgre, Angular.
- Teamsize: 3 Frontend, 3 Backend, 1 BA.

EDUCATION

2017 - 2021

Ho Chi Minh City Open University

• Major: Computer Science